{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:36:19.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:36:09.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7198,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:36:10.332000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:35:19.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:35:12.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7197,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:35:13.037000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:34:39.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:34:17.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7196,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:34:17.731000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:33:38.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:33:22.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7195,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:33:23.209000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:32:38.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:32:26.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7194,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:32:27.209000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:31:37.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:31:31.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7193,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:31:32.077000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:30:57.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:30:36.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7192,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:30:36.882000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:29:57.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:29:40.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7191,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:29:41.404000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:28:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:28:45.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7190,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:28:46.272000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:27:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:27:50.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7189,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:27:50.724000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:27:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:27:42.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"HSimpson@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"SSEDEMOMANAGED","PublicIPv4":"20.106.90.84","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.44","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"b5532f4b-68f0-4cf6-be0a-a7a1e9f9fadf","EndpointSN":"0000-0014-8689-2559-2181-0343-51","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7188,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:27:43.258000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:27:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:27:42.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"HSimpson@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"SSEDEMOMANAGED","PublicIPv4":"20.106.90.84","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"b5532f4b-68f0-4cf6-be0a-a7a1e9f9fadf","EndpointSN":"0000-0014-8689-2559-2181-0343-51","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 11ms, Post-tunnel latency: 1ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7187,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:27:43.251000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:27:16.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:26:55.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7186,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:26:55.746000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:26:15.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:25:59.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7185,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:25:59.854000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:25:15.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:25:03.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7184,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:25:04.043000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:24:15.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:24:07.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7183,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:24:08.265000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:23:35.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:23:11.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7182,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:23:12.059000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:22:34.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:22:15.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7181,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:22:16.244000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:21:34.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:21:20.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7180,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:21:21.094000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:20:34.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:20:25.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7179,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:20:26.340000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:19:33.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:19:29.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7178,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:19:29.487000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:18:53.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:18:34.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7177,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:18:34.627000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:17:53.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:17:39.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7176,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:17:39.607000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:16:53.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:16:43.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7175,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:16:44.300000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:15:52.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:15:48.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7174,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:15:48.826000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:15:12.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:14:52.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7173,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:14:52.974000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:14:39.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:14:25.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"CStewart@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-cstewa","PublicIPv4":"104.43.208.158","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.25","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"6070680d-9022-4ed5-87ed-75831899b990","EndpointSN":"0000-0014-1539-2941-6853-3096-08","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1551,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:14:26.346000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:14:39.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:14:25.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"CStewart@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-cstewa","PublicIPv4":"104.43.208.158","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"6070680d-9022-4ed5-87ed-75831899b990","EndpointSN":"0000-0014-1539-2941-6853-3096-08","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 34ms, Post-tunnel latency: 16ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1550,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:14:26.340000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:14:12.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:13:56.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7172,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:13:56.953000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:13:12.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:13:01.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7171,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:13:01.368000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:12:11.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:12:05.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7170,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:12:05.444000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:11:31.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:11:09.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7169,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:11:09.318000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:11:11.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:10:55.000000Z","VirtualSystem":null,"EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-report","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"DESKTOP-TADJ949","PublicIPv4":"8.47.64.2","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.9","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"b9717cf6-6f45-4622-9cfb-e3ce1d2e491a","EndpointSN":"VMware-42 1a e9 98 53 0c 62 a5-f1 57 27 16 90 f9 01 39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":null,"EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7168,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:10:56.216000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":0,"DGHierarchyLevel2":0,"DGHierarchyLevel3":0,"DGHierarchyLevel4":0,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":0}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:11:11.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:10:55.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"DESKTOP-TADJ949","PublicIPv4":"8.47.64.2","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.9","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"b9717cf6-6f45-4622-9cfb-e3ce1d2e491a","EndpointSN":"VMware-42 1a e9 98 53 0c 62 a5-f1 57 27 16 90 f9 01 39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7167,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:10:56.107000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:11:11.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:10:55.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"DESKTOP-TADJ949","PublicIPv4":"8.47.64.2","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"b9717cf6-6f45-4622-9cfb-e3ce1d2e491a","EndpointSN":"VMware-42 1a e9 98 53 0c 62 a5-f1 57 27 16 90 f9 01 39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 24ms, Post-tunnel latency: 16ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7166,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:10:56.097000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:10:30.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:10:14.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7165,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:10:14.777000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:09:50.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:09:28.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7164,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:09:29.216000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:09:50.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:09:28.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 14ms, Post-tunnel latency: -1ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7163,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:09:29.208000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:09:29.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:09:19.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7162,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:09:19.622000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:08:28.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:08:23.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7161,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:08:23.843000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:07:48.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:07:27.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7160,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:07:27.977000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:06:47.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:06:31.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7159,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:06:32.189000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:05:47.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:05:37.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7158,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:05:37.791000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:04:46.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:04:41.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7157,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:04:42.066000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:04:10.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:03:50.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-dmodi","PublicIPv4":"20.106.167.98","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.64.21","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"58409473-0626-404f-a4e5-9c0e237de505","EndpointSN":"0000-0011-0711-7876-4147-5105-61","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1406,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:03:50.317000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193476_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:04:10.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:03:50.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-dmodi","PublicIPv4":"20.106.167.98","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"58409473-0626-404f-a4e5-9c0e237de505","EndpointSN":"0000-0011-0711-7876-4147-5105-61","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 4ms, Post-tunnel latency: 1ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1405,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:03:50.312000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193476_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:04:06.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:03:46.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7156,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:03:46.365000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:03:06.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:02:51.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7155,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:02:51.391000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:02:06.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:01:55.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7154,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:01:55.574000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:01:15.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:00:56.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-logout","Stage":"logout","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"CStewart@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Nishit-Win-1","PublicIPv4":"40.77.65.16","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.21","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"16b16d22-ec79-4cc1-859c-a5626df3d1eb","EndpointSN":"0000-0004-3793-3765-4151-3685-68","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Windows","EndpointOSVersion":"Microsoft Windows 10 Enterprise for Virtual Desktops , 64-bit","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"client logout, Logout From: 165.1.179.17","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":5286,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1549,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:00:57.024000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:01:15.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:00:56.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-config-release","Stage":"configuration","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"CStewart@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Nishit-Win-1","PublicIPv4":"40.77.65.16","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.21","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"16b16d22-ec79-4cc1-859c-a5626df3d1eb","EndpointSN":"0000-0004-3793-3765-4151-3685-68","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Windows","EndpointOSVersion":"Microsoft Windows 10 Enterprise for Virtual Desktops , 64-bit","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":null,"EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1548,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:00:57.024000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:01:06.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:01:00.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7153,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:01:00.848000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T20:00:25.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T20:00:05.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7152,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T20:00:05.639000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:59:23.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:59:09.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7151,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:59:10.068000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:59:03.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:58:41.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-logout","Stage":"logout","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.41","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"client logout, Logout From: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":966,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7150,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:58:41.802000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:59:03.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:58:41.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-config-release","Stage":"configuration","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.41","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":null,"EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7149,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:58:41.802000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:58:23.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:58:13.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7148,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:58:14.135000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:57:22.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:57:18.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7147,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:57:18.753000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:56:41.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:56:23.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7146,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:56:23.929000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:55:41.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:55:27.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7145,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:55:27.806000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:54:47.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:54:26.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"HSimpson@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike iPad Pro","PublicIPv4":"66.31.121.50","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.64.16","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"539DC81396F144FE9245D70813911A61","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1404,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:54:26.975000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193476_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:54:47.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:54:26.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"HSimpson@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike iPad Pro","PublicIPv4":"66.31.121.50","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"539DC81396F144FE9245D70813911A61","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 33ms, Post-tunnel latency: 28ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1403,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:54:26.972000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193476_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:54:41.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:54:31.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7144,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:54:31.995000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:54:00.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:53:36.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7143,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:53:36.951000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:53:00.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:52:41.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7142,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:52:41.484000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:52:00.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:51:46.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7141,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:51:46.415000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:50:59.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:50:50.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7140,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:50:50.722000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:49:58.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:49:55.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7139,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:49:55.570000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:49:19.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:49:00.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7138,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:49:00.343000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:48:53.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:48:32.000000Z","VirtualSystem":null,"EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-report","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.22","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":null,"EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1547,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:48:32.431000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":0,"DGHierarchyLevel2":0,"DGHierarchyLevel3":0,"DGHierarchyLevel4":0,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":0}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:48:53.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:48:31.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.22","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1546,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:48:32.286000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:48:53.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:48:31.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 24ms, Post-tunnel latency: 31ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1545,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:48:32.283000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:48:31.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:48:13.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.22","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1544,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:48:14.368000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:48:31.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:48:13.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 24ms, Post-tunnel latency: 31ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1543,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:48:14.362000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:48:18.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:48:04.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7137,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:48:04.278000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:47:31.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:47:12.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"CStewart@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Nishit-Win-1","PublicIPv4":"40.77.65.16","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.21","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"16b16d22-ec79-4cc1-859c-a5626df3d1eb","EndpointSN":"0000-0004-3793-3765-4151-3685-68","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1542,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:47:13.305000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:47:31.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:47:12.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"CStewart@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Nishit-Win-1","PublicIPv4":"40.77.65.16","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"16b16d22-ec79-4cc1-859c-a5626df3d1eb","EndpointSN":"0000-0004-3793-3765-4151-3685-68","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 24ms, Post-tunnel latency: 31ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1541,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:47:13.299000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:47:18.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:47:08.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7136,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:47:08.878000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:46:18.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:46:13.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7135,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:46:13.512000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:45:38.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:45:18.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7134,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:45:18.753000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:45:04.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:44:52.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"ECollin@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"M-C02Y50FNJGH8","PublicIPv4":"66.31.121.50","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.64.2","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"38:f9:d3:73:b9:25","EndpointSN":"C02Y50FNJGH8","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1402,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:44:53.180000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193476_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:45:04.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:44:52.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"ECollin@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"M-C02Y50FNJGH8","PublicIPv4":"66.31.121.50","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"38:f9:d3:73:b9:25","EndpointSN":"C02Y50FNJGH8","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 41ms, Post-tunnel latency: -1ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1401,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:44:53.174000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193476_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:44:37.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:44:22.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7133,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:44:23.099000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:44:17.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:44:03.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"ECollin@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"TEMPLATE-WIN10","PublicIPv4":"8.47.64.2","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.4","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"291d6831-7393-477b-a0b9-ea12bca1bc42","EndpointSN":"VMware-42 1a f0 7e 14 e4 70 ae-e0 3e 64 5f f2 9d f2 55","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7132,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:44:03.599000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:44:17.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:44:03.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"ECollin@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"TEMPLATE-WIN10","PublicIPv4":"8.47.64.2","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"291d6831-7393-477b-a0b9-ea12bca1bc42","EndpointSN":"VMware-42 1a f0 7e 14 e4 70 ae-e0 3e 64 5f f2 9d f2 55","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 14ms, Post-tunnel latency: 16ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7131,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:44:03.592000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:43:57.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:43:39.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"HSimpson@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"DEMO1-PC","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.36","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"3c89bce1-c336-4a00-ab1d-622580e00f80","EndpointSN":"VMware-56 4d a5 5d 45 a6 1e 09-ac 48 18 a8 25 7b 9b ec","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7130,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:43:39.979000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:43:57.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:43:39.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"HSimpson@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"DEMO1-PC","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"3c89bce1-c336-4a00-ab1d-622580e00f80","EndpointSN":"VMware-56 4d a5 5d 45 a6 1e 09-ac 48 18 a8 25 7b 9b ec","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 39ms, Post-tunnel latency: 15ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7129,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:43:39.971000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:43:37.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:43:27.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7128,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:43:27.663000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","VirtualSystem":null,"EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-report","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.41","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":null,"EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7127,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.522000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":0,"DGHierarchyLevel2":0,"DGHierarchyLevel3":0,"DGHierarchyLevel4":0,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":0}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.41","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7126,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.391000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 17ms, Post-tunnel latency: 14ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7125,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.387000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-connected","Stage":"connected","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"IPSec","SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.41","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7124,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.386000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-setup-ipsec","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"IPSec","SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.41","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7123,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.385000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:35.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-getconfig","Stage":"configuration","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"IPSec","SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.41","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Config name: Partners-Tunnel, Client region: US.","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7122,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:35.979000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:35.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-register","Stage":"login","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7121,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:35.818000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:35.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-auth","Stage":"login","AuthMethod":"Cookie","TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":"on-demand","ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7120,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:35.805000Z","GatewaySelectionType":"auto","SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:35.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-prelogin","Stage":"before-login","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":null,"SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":null,"PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7119,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:35.677000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:36.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:32.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7118,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:32.536000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:34.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:33.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"portal-getconfig","Stage":"configuration","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Config name: Partners-AppConfig, Machine Certificate CN : (null)","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":"on-demand","ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_Portal","SequenceNo":1720,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:34.023000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPPT_193472_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:34.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:33.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"portal-auth","Stage":"login","AuthMethod":"SAML","TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":null,"EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_Portal","SequenceNo":1719,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:33.995000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPPT_193472_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:34.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:33.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"portal-gen-cookie","Stage":"login","AuthMethod":"SAML","TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"DModi@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"ebob9 iPad","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":null,"EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_Portal","SequenceNo":1718,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:33.995000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPPT_193472_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:42:34.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:42:23.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"portal-prelogin","Stage":"before-login","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":null,"SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":null,"PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"F716DD6F1B364C99B657AA4B057C158F","EndpointSN":null,"GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.9","EndpointOSType":"iOS","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple iOS 14.7.1","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":null,"EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_Portal","SequenceNo":1717,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:42:24.412000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPPT_193472_us-east-1_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:41:56.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:41:37.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7117,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:41:37.413000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:41:30.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:41:14.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.22","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1540,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:41:14.748000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:41:30.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:41:14.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 24ms, Post-tunnel latency: 31ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1539,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:41:14.728000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:41:30.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:41:14.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-connected","Stage":"connected","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"IPSec","SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.22","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Windows","EndpointOSVersion":"Microsoft Windows 10 Pro , 64-bit","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 165.1.179.17","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1538,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:41:14.727000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:41:30.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:41:14.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-setup-ipsec","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"IPSec","SourceUserName":"EWard@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Mike-HIP-2","PublicIPv4":"40.122.193.74","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.68.22","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"0a6c5783-07a4-488d-8e1e-8d45b2b1354c","EndpointSN":"0000-0006-9705-5054-4544-7762-39","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Windows","EndpointOSVersion":"Microsoft Windows 10 Pro , 64-bit","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 165.1.179.17","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":1537,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:41:14.726000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193480_us-east-2_649068640","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:40:55.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:40:42.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7116,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:40:42.302000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:39:55.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:39:46.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7115,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:39:46.908000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:39:55.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:39:31.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-hip-check","Stage":"host-info","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"HSimpson@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"SSEDEMOUNMNG","PublicIPv4":"20.106.88.124","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.43","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"b5532f4b-68f0-4cf6-be0a-a7a1e9f9fadf","EndpointSN":"0000-0018-2534-4783-9892-3909-10","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"HIP report is not needed","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7114,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:39:31.178000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:39:55.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:39:31.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-tunnel-latency","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":null,"SourceUserName":"HSimpson@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":null,"EndpointDeviceName":"SSEDEMOUNMNG","PublicIPv4":"20.106.88.124","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"b5532f4b-68f0-4cf6-be0a-a7a1e9f9fadf","EndpointSN":"0000-0018-2534-4783-9892-3909-10","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":null,"EndpointOSVersion":null,"CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Pre-tunnel latency: 9ms, Post-tunnel latency: 1ms","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7113,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:39:31.170000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:39:15.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:38:51.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7112,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:38:51.475000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:38:14.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:37:55.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7111,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:37:55.997000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:37:14.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:37:00.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7110,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:37:00.849000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
{"TimeReceived":"2021-09-23T19:36:14.000000Z","DeviceSN":"no-serial","LogType":"GLOBALPROTECT","LogSubtype":"globalprotect","ConfigVersion":"10.0","TimeGenerated":"2021-09-23T19:36:05.000000Z","VirtualSystem":"vsys1","EventIDValue":"gateway-switch-to-ssl","Stage":"tunnel","AuthMethod":null,"TunnelType":"SSLVPN","SourceUserName":"msingh@alvisofincorp.com","SourceRegion":"US","EndpointDeviceName":"Demos-Mac","PublicIPv4":"199.167.54.229","PublicIPv6":"","PrivateIPv4":"172.31.66.40","PrivateIPv6":"","HostID":"00:0c:29:f7:e2:34","EndpointSN":"VMeMkr11VCio","GlobalProtectClientVersion":"5.2.8","EndpointOSType":"Mac","EndpointOSVersion":"Apple Mac OS X 11.6.0","CountOfRepeats":1,"QuarantineReason":null,"ConnectionError":null,"Description":"Login to: 208.127.85.222","EventStatus":"success","GlobalProtectGatewayLocation":null,"LoginDuration":0,"ConnectionMethod":null,"ConnectionErrorID":0,"Portal":"GlobalProtect_External_Gateway","SequenceNo":7109,"TimeGeneratedHighResolution":"2021-09-23T19:36:05.311000Z","GatewaySelectionType":null,"SSLResponseTime":-1,"GatewayPriority":null,"AttemptedGateways":null,"Gateway":null,"DGHierarchyLevel1":65536,"DGHierarchyLevel2":65537,"DGHierarchyLevel3":65571,"DGHierarchyLevel4":65540,"VirtualSystemName":null,"DeviceName":"GPGW_193478_us-west-201_6490686","VirtualSystemID":1}
